



Hi! I'm STUDENT Michaela Majorošová

miselka12345@gmail.com

+421 949 327 913

27.01.2003

Driver's licence class B

Slovakia | Košice | O44 57

As a 20-year-old student of Košice Academy of Software Development (KASV), I have a deep passion for working in the field of Information Technology. I particularly enjoy the creative aspects of web design and the challenges posed by both front-end and back-end development.

Education

2022-now Kosice academy of software development

Computer systems

2018-2022 Grammar school of St. Thomas

Aquinas

Graduation subjects: Slovak language, English language, economics, informatics

2013-2014 Art School

Audiovisual and multimedia production

Work Experience

2022-2023 Pizza Delivery

2021-2022 School company, JA

Slovensko

2021-2022 Bolt Food

2018-2021 Animator

- Animator in camps since 2018
- Animator in Steam Factory 2020-2021

Skills

HTML

CSS

Java

Python

PHP

Angular

React

Firestore

Mongo DB

MySQL

Filmora, Vegas

Canva

Office

Certificate

Junior Achievement (JA) Slovensko

Languages

Slovak

English

German